<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>Chirpy</title><subtitle>A minimal, portfolio, sidebar, bootstrap Jekyll theme with responsive web design and focuses on text presentation.</subtitle> <updated>2021-10-13T14:58:11-04:00</updated> <author> <name>your_full_name</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2021 your_full_name </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>Installing Openwrt</title><link href="/posts/Installing-OpenWRT/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Installing Openwrt" /><published>2021-10-13T00:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2021-10-13T00:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>/posts/Installing-OpenWRT/</id> <content src="/posts/Installing-OpenWRT/" /> <author> <name>your_full_name</name> </author> <summary> Installing OpenWRT Into my Network, with TinyProxy, VPN, And Pi-Hole. I replaced the stock firmware from my router with OpenWRT, this provides me a lot more control over my router, and allows me to learn more about managing a network. The first thing I did was perform dns hijacking against myself. This is because applications were able to bypass my Pi-Hole local dns resolver. Pi-Hole is a loc... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Pihole Traffic Analysis</title><link href="/posts/PiHole-Traffic-Analysis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pihole Traffic Analysis" /><published>2021-10-12T00:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2021-10-12T00:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>/posts/PiHole-Traffic-Analysis/</id> <content src="/posts/PiHole-Traffic-Analysis/" /> <author> <name>your_full_name</name> </author> <summary> Analyzing Traffic With Pi-Hole and Proxifier. Proxifier showed me the currently active connections that applications were running in the background, and what applications were responsible. It made me learn more about my applications since I looked them up online, and if I didn’t need those connections I would block them. With pihole I had a lot more control to learn about what domains can be ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Pygame Mod</title><link href="/posts/Pygame-Mod/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pygame Mod" /><published>2021-10-11T00:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2021-10-11T00:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>/posts/Pygame-Mod/</id> <content src="/posts/Pygame-Mod/" /> <author> <name>your_full_name</name> </author> <summary> Pygame Slide Puzzle Mod I had a simple college assignment to make a modified version of a Pygame called Slide Puzzle (by Al Sweigart). This pygame only works on Windows. (Install with “pip install pypiwin32”, for any win32api issues use Google) How to play: The board is a 4x4 grid with fifteen tiles (numbered 1 through 15 going left to right) and one blank space. The tiles start out in rando... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Live Obs Camera</title><link href="/posts/Live-OBS-Camera/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Live Obs Camera" /><published>2021-10-09T00:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2021-10-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>/posts/Live-OBS-Camera/</id> <content src="/posts/Live-OBS-Camera/" /> <author> <name>your_full_name</name> </author> <summary> Making a Live Security Camera with OBS. In December 2019, I was committed to turning my old mobile device into a live security camera. Simply because I was bored. This could be done simply with two applications, obs and droidcam, droidcam would send the camera feed from my phone to obs. The only problem now is that obs is made to livestream to the internet. I had to learn how to make my server... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Jupyter Notebook</title><link href="/posts/Jupyter-Notebook/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jupyter Notebook" /><published>2021-10-08T00:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2021-10-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>/posts/Jupyter-Notebook/</id> <content src="/posts/Jupyter-Notebook/" /> <author> <name>your_full_name</name> </author> <summary> Analyzing and Comparing data with Jupyter Notebook I was taught to use Juniper Notebook in order to compare data and suggest what application a company should develop, in order to get the most benefit. There are three sets of instructions on how to do the assignment. The summarized version is heavily edited by me. The chippy version has some edits. The normal version is the original one given... </summary> </entry> </feed>
